I am starting a monthly at Comedy in Harlem on every second Wednesday of the month.
Oh, you are?
And yeah, because I did my Truth Translator sound session at Comedy in Harlem.
Shout out to Jamie.
You know, Jamie was like, yeah, come through, do whatever you want.
So I led folks in a energy, like in a Qigong energy practice through the album.
And then after that, they could ask questions.
And I basically did stand up for 30 minutes, essentially, because if you're talking to me, I'm going to have jokes.
Oh, you were funny.
I saw the clip of you when you did that song.
I mean, Amanda can't help, but like you could see she was holding off.
But then eventually she's going to be funny.
You know, I mean, she can't help it.
It's there.